声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
我想...我想我没事了
I think...I think I'm all right.
我告诉过你我会照顾好你的
I told you I'd take care of you.
-谢谢你  Charlie  -你太客气了
-Thanks,Charlie.  -You're quite welcome.
-听我说  -Sayid!
-Listen to me.  -Sayid!
岛上不只我们这些人
We're not alone.
我在睡觉  刚醒来
I was sleeping,and I woke up,and
他正要伤害我的孩子
he was trying to hurt my baby.
我们得查明每个人的身份
We gotta find out who everyone is.
你想人口调查
You want to start a census.
-Lance!  -什么?
-Lance!  -Sorry?
你叫Lance  对吧?
Your name's Lance,right?
-Ethan  -老兄  你说得对!
-Ethan.  -Dude,that's right.
我要你服这些药
I want you to take these.
这些是非常温和的镇静剂
They're sedatives,very mild.
你认为这些都是我编造出来的?
You think I'm making this up?
海边要安全点  这儿不够安全
It was safe at the beach. It's not safe here.
你对她说什么了?
What did you say to her?
发现个问题  有关人口调查的
We got a problem. The census.
我会见了每个人
I interviewed everyone.
其中一位并不在旅客名单上
One of them isn't in the manifest.
他没在飞机上
He wasn't on the plane.
-他不在飞机上  -谁不在飞机上?
-He wasn't on the plane.  -Who wasn't on the plane?
Ethan  那个来自加拿大的家伙  他不在旅客名单之列
Ethan,the Canadian guy. He's not on the passenger manifest.
-那他在哪?  -我不知道
-Where the hell is he?  -I don't know.
-我昨天还看见过他  -有人看见Ethan了吗?
-I saw him yesterday... -Has anyone seen Ethan?
是的  他去砍柴了  在去海边的路上
Yeah,yeah,he went to get some wood. Took off on the path to the beach.
他没事吧?  发生什么事了?
Is he okay? What happened?
-Charlie在哪儿?  -什么?
-Where's Charlie?  -What?
Charlie在哪?
Where's Charlie?
他去追Claire了
He went after Claire.
Jack!
她正要搬回到海边去住
She was moving back to the beach.
Claire...是她的东西
Claire...that's hers.
发生什么事了?  他们去哪了?
What happened? Where are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
脚印
Footprints.
这地方至少有三种不同的脚印
At least three distinct sets all over the place.
看起来像是有过争斗
It looks like there might have been a struggle.
什么?  又有什么?
What? What is it?
这儿有拖痕...
Drag marks here...
这儿也有
and here.
Claire和Charlie...
Claire and Charlie...
他们在一起
they were together.
我想他们被挟持走了
I think they've been taken.
-Charlie!  -Jack
嘘...
Shh.
这些痕迹是刚弄上去的
The tracks are still fresh.
这一点儿都不合理
This doesn't make any sense.
一个人怎么拖得动两个  其中一个还是怀孕的?
How could one man drag off two people,one of them pregnant?
你问错问题了  不是怎么拖  而是为什么?
You're asking the wrong question. Not how,why?
你认为是Ethan干的?
You think it was Ethan?
感觉当然是Ethan  难道不是吗?
Certainly feels like it was Ethan,doesn't it?
靠他一个人?  怎么拖?
By himself? How?
我们无法解释我们中的所有人
We can't account for all of our people.
更重要的是  谁说他们是我们的人了?
And more importantly,who's to say they're even our people?
Sayid说还有其他人
Sayid said there were others.
-Sayid只说我们并不孤独  -他就这个意思
-Sayid said that we're not alone.  -Semantics.
Sayid受伤了  我们甚至不知道他去过哪  他现在神智不清
Sayid's injured. We don't even know where he went. He's delirious.
我只是在告诉你地面给我的一些暗示
I'm just telling you what the ground is telling me.
那地面告诉你他们往哪条路走了?
So which way is the ground telling you that they went?
Jack  我们不知道这儿发生过什么事
Jack,we don't know what's going on here.
我们知道得够多了
We know enough.
我们需要准备准备  10分钟内我们就能回到山洞
We need to prepare. We could be back at the caves in 10 minutes,
-组织搜索队...  -他们朝哪边走了  Locke?
-organize a search party...  -Which way did they go,Locke?
斯达数下降
Stats are dropping.
血压下降  她在不停的流血
B.P.'S falling. She's bleeding out.
不  我已经止住动脉的血了
No,I've got the artery almost there.
心脏停止跳动
She's in arrest.
一毫克EPI  把电击车推过来
One milligram epi. Let's get the crash cart over here!
好的  动脉缝合了  继续缝合
All right,artery's sealed. Close her up.
电击板
Defib.
-充电?  -充电完毕
-Charged?  -Charged.
开始
Clear.
-充电?  -充电完毕
-Charged?  -We're charged.
开始
Clear.
加油
Come on.
加油  恢复心跳  加油
Come on back now. Come on.
加油
Come on now.
加油  回来吧
Come on back.
加油
Come on.
到此为止
Call it.
加油  宝贝  回来吧  回来
Come on,baby. Come back. Come back.
加油  宝贝  加油
Come on,baby. Come on.
加油
Come on now.
加油  宝贝  加油
You can do this. Come on.
加油
Come on.
行了  Jack
Call it,Jack.
结束了  停止吧
It's over. Call it.
算你行
You call it.
你让他一个人去找?
You let him go alone?
别担心  我会赶上他的
Don't worry,I'll catch up.
海边的人有什么消息吗?
What's the word from the beach?
没有  没人看到过他
Nothing. Nobody has seen him.
-我和你一起去  -我就知道你会的
-I'm coming with you.  -I figured you might.
我们取水后得回到海边去
We need to get our water and get back to the beach.
听说你在组织一支搜索队  我能帮上什么忙吗?
I heard you're forming a search party. Can I help?
这是个荒岛
This is a deserted island.
没直升机  没报警系统
There's no choppers,no amber alerts.
你说你怎么找他们?
How exactly are you gonna find them?
跟踪Ethan的足迹
By following Ethan's trail.
没人能够不留痕迹的穿越这片荒野
No one can walk through the wilderness without leaving signs...
草的弯曲  折断的树枝
bending blades of grass,breaking twigs...
尤其是还拖着两个家伙
especially with captives in tow.
还有  如果你肯来的话我还能多个帮手
And yes,I could use another hand if you're up for it.
那么我们出发吧
Then let's get moving.
我可以带着Vincent一块去
I could take Vincent,
他能够嗅出属于Charlie的东西
and he can sniff something that belonged to Charlie,
我帮得上忙
and I can help.
我说过不行  小子
I said no,man.
Locke
听着  你知道大伙都不愿干坐着等消息
hey,look,you know,a lot us don't just wanna sit here waiting for news.
谢谢  但我们人手够了  再多个人只会减慢搜寻速度
Thanks,but we're set. Anyone else is just gonna slow us down.
或许我能再组织一支搜寻队
Maybe I'll just put together another party.
好主意
Good idea.
我们去北边找  我建议你去南边
We're going North. I suggest you go South.
我们走
Come on.
我从没想过会看到这一天  Jack
Never thought I'd see the day,Jack.
你闯进我的手术室  给我的病人动手术
You barge into my O.R. You work on my patient.
你不必接这个急诊的
You didn't have to do this procedure.
我什么都不必做
I don't have to do anything.
是  你当然不必
Yeah,of course you don't.
我接手做这个手术
I chose to do this procedure...
这个紧急手术
this emergency procedure...
是因为女孩被送到急诊室的时候  他们打电话给我
because when this girl crashed in the E.R.,they called me.
我就在楼上
I was right upstairs.
你应该在楼上的  你怎么知道这些的?
You should have stayed upstairs. And how did you find out?
有个护士过来告诉我的
One of the nurses came to get me.
谁?
Who?
感谢上帝  有你和某个匿名的护士救我
Oh,thank god I have you and some anonymous nurse to rescue me.
她告诉我你的手在发抖
She told me that your hands were shaking.
-我的手没...  -你切断了她的肝动脉
-My hands were not...  -You cut her hepatic artery.
她被车撞了  Jack  她的身体内部一团糟
She was in a car crash,Jack. Her insides were a mess.
-你犯了个错误  -他们打电话给我的
-You made a mistake.  -They called me.
我才不管他们是否打电话给你
I don't care whether or not they called you,
-你犯了个错误  -你在对我说教?
-you made a mistake.  -Are you lecturing me?
如果你在楼上  而我在饭店吃午饭
If you were upstairs,and I was in a restaurant having lunch,
那他们为什么要打电话给我?
then why did they call me?
你中午喝了多少酒  爸爸?
How many drinks did you have at lunch,dad?
Jack!
幸好你在原地找
It's a good thing you were going in a circle.
没到更大的范围去
Not much of a search grid,but
否则我们怎么都找不到你了
we never would have found ya otherwise.
有什么发现吗?
Did you find anything?
你应该回到山洞去  Sayid的腿有伤
You should go back to the caves...Sayid's leg.
我给Sayid的腿敷过药了
I dressed Sayid's leg.
你找得到我  我们也能找到Charlie和Claire
You found me. We can find Charlie and Claire.
我们还有没有足迹可以跟踪?
Now,do we have a trail to follow or not?
-Jack  这都是我的错  -什么?
-Jack,this was my fault.  -What?
我和Ethan一块儿打猎  我和他度过了很长时间
I hunted with Ethan,I spent time with him.
我什么都没察觉出来
I never sensed anything...off.
但就我对打猎和跟踪的了解
But for everything that I know about hunting and tracking,
不管这人是谁  他知道得很多
whoever he is,he knows more.
如果我们追上他了
If we catch up with him,
我不想岛上唯一一个训练有素的医生发生什么意外
I don't want anything to happen to the only trained physician on the island.
所以还是回去当好医生吧  让我去找他
So go back,be the doctor. Let me be the hunter.
我们可以走了吗?
Can we go now?
跟着我
Follow me.
我尽力想帮忙  那家伙却叫我去南边?
I'm trying to help,and all the guy can tell me is go South?
什么话嘛?  我碍着他们了还是怎么了?
Like what? I'm gonna get in his way or something?
我们都很焦急  老兄
We're all tweaked,man.
Locke也和其他人一样
Locke's just feeling it like the rest of us.
那又怎样?
So what?
那儿有五个家伙会和我一块儿去
I got five guys who are going out there with me,
就算冒着生命危险  我们也想去找Charlie和Claire
putting our necks on the line to try to find Charlie and Claire.
我想说的是
All I'm saying is
我讨厌在这儿被当成二等公民
I'm getting sick of being treated like a second-class citizen around here
就因为那秃头能抓野猪
because Mount Baldy can bag a boar.
除了抓野猪  他还知道很多
He knows a lot more than how to catch a boar.
Locke先生是个勇士
Mr. Locke's a warrior...
他能打猎
he can hunt,
他能跟踪  他是这儿唯一一个带刀子的人
he can track stuff,and he's the only one who brought knives.
所以如果是我  我就会听他的
So if it were me,I'd listen to him.
我不想你听他的
Well,I don't want you to.
明白吗?
You understand?
你和Hurley呆一块儿
You stay with Hurley.
我或许不是个勇士  但我会去南边
I might not be a warrior,but I am going South.
等我回到家
Back home,
大家也会认为我是个勇士的
I'm known as something of a warrior myself.
我们用红线标记我们的行程
We mark our progress by line of sight.
把这个绑在树上  我们就不会迷路了
Tie these off so we don't get lost.
你能带我们回营地  对吧?
You can lead us back to camp,right?
如果我没发生什么意外的话
If nothing happens to me.
或许由我来做标记会更好一些
Maybe I'd better take marker detail.
有发现?
Anything?
还没
Not yet.
-如果你找不到踪迹...  -我会再找到的
-If you can't find the trail...  -I'll pick it up again.
我们得休息会儿好让思路清晰一些
We need to rest for a minute,to get our clarity back.
你们要休息?
You're gonna take a break?
快4:00点了  太阳一下山就不可能...
It's gotta be almost 4:00. When the sun sets,there's no way...
现在是4:25  但我要休息一下
It's 4:25. And,yes,I'm taking a break.
我和你谈谈?
Can I talk to you for a sec?
给他点空间  这又不会对你怎么样
Would it kill you to give the guy a little space?
会的
It might.
不要那样
Stop that.
那样
That.
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
我没有相信她...Claire
I didn't believe her...Claire.
-我给了她镇定药  -Jack  你不能...
-I gave her a sedative.  -Jack,you can't...
她告诉我有人在追她  有人要伤害她  我却..
she told me someone was after her,that she was being attacked,and I...
感觉她说的有点脱节
she just seemed so out of it.
我以为是怀孕增加了她的压力的缘故  我...
I thought that her pregnancy was amping up her stress,and I...
我没有相信她
I didn't believe her.
Jack!
什么?
What is it?
很熟悉吧?
Look familiar?
是Charlie的
It's Charlie's.
你觉得这只是个意外的发现吗?
You think it just came off?
他在给我们暗示
He's leaving us a trail.
他们朝这边走了
They went this way.
我不是很确定
I'm not so sure.
这儿有另一个线索
There's another trail here.
-你什么意思  "另一个"?  -这些是脚印
-What do you mean,"another"?  -These are footprints.
他们朝这边移动
People moved off this way.
Charlie留下这些给我们作暗示
Charlie's leaving these for us to follow.
他们往那边去了
They went that way.
除非这些东西不是Charlie留下的
Unless Charlie isn't the one leaving them.
如果Ethan知道我们在跟踪他  他很可能会弄些假线索
If Ethan knows that we're behind him,he could be setting up a dummy trail.
在一个方向岔开  然后沿着原脚印往回走
Take off in one direction,double back in his old footprints.
等等  你也会跟踪?
Wait,now you're a tracker?
你真让人惊讶
You're just full of surprises.
所以我们有两条路可走
So we've got two trails.
我们分头找吧  我找这边
Let's split up. I'll take that one.
不行  我们得呆在一起  Jack
No,we should stay together,Jack.
为什么?  我们有两个线索  而且有两个会跟踪的人
Why? We've got two trails,and apparently two trackers.
小心点
Be careful.
谁被谁挟持走了?
Who got taken by what?
Charlie和Claire  他们都认为是Ethan干的
Charlie and Claire. They think Ethan took 'em.
-Ethan挟持他们?  -是的
-Ethan took 'em?  -Yeah.
为什么要挟持他们?  还有Ethan是谁?
Took 'em why? And who the hell's Ethan?
我不知道  他不在旅客名单上
I don't know. He wasn't on the list thing,the manifest.
有没想过  他有可能虚报他的名字?
Ever think he might have lied about his name?
虚报名字那太蠢了
It's stupid to lie about your name.
好吧  小子
All right,tattoo,
那你觉得Ethan从哪儿来的?
where do you think Ethan came from?
可能在我们来之前  他就在岛上了
Maybe he was already on the island before we were.
你可真会想象  孩子
Got yourself one hell of an imagination,kid.
岛上可能有许多人
There could be lots of other people on the island.
所以当地的邪恶部落派了个人潜入我们的营地
So a tribe of evil natives planted a ringer in the camp
来绑架一个孕妇  而且这女子还是VH1电台扔在这儿的
to kidnap a pregnant girl and a reject from VH1 has-beens.
是的  简直太聪明了
Yeah,fiendishly clever.
为什么我要听一个6岁小子的话?
And why am I getting the evening news from a 6-year-old?
我10岁
I'm 10.
好吧  这就一定是真的了
Okay,then it must be true.
如果你不相信我  问问Sayid  他说岛上不只我们这些人
If you don't believe me,ask Sayid. He said we're not alone.
Sayid回来了?
Sayid's back?
-红衬衫  -啊?
-Red shirt.  -Huh?
红衬衫  你看过"星际之门"吗?
Red shirt. You ever watch "Star Trek"?
没看过
Oh,not really.
跟着一队人来到一个星球...
that would go down to the planet with the main guys...
首长和那个有尖耳朵的家伙
the captain and the guy with the pointy ears...
他们总穿着红衬衫  而且老是被杀
they always wore red shirts,and they always got killed.
-是吗?  -是的
-Yeah?  -Yeah.
听起来像是个可怜的首长
Sounds like a pisspoor captain.
在现实生活中你是干什么的  Locke先生?
What do you doin the real world,Mr. Locke?
-叫我John  -John
-It's John.  -John.
猜猜看?
Why don't you guess?
你要么是动物标本剥制师  要么就是职业杀手
Well,you're either a taxidermist or a hit man.
我是...
I was a...
包装箱公司的区域收集监督人员
regional collections supervisor for a box company.
包装箱公司?
A box company?
他们做盒子的
They made boxes.
是吗
Yeah,right.
-慢一点!  -你说他们朝这边走的
-Please slow down!  -You said they went this way.
我想他们朝这边走的  我没Locke那么厉害
I think they went this way. I'm not as good at this as Locke is.
这些跟踪技术你是哪里学来的  Kate?
So where'd you pick up the tracking skills,Kate?
是在通缉前还是通缉后学的?
Was that before or after you were on the run?
-我试着帮忙  Jack  -你知道什么东西帮得上忙?
-I'm trying to help,Jack.  -You know what might help?
诚实一点
A little honesty.
给我些真实的东西...任何东西都可以
Just give me something real --anything.
我爸爸是军队里的
My dad was in the army...
突击队
ranger battalion.
他驻扎在华盛顿州的路易丝堡
He was stationed at Fort Lewis,Washington State.
我们曾经一块儿远足
We'd go hiking together.
有一天  我们花了8个小时追一只鹿
One day we spent eight hours tracking deer.
呆在丛林里  感觉就像...
Being in the woods,it was like...
就像是他的宗教信仰
it was like his religion.
那是真实的
That was real.
你有什么要分享的吗  Jack?
Anything you wanna share,Jack?
感谢你能来  Jack  请坐
Well,thanks for coming in,Jack. Have a seat.
纸上写了什么?
What's it say?
事实
The truth...
发生车祸后  病人被送到了急诊室
that a patient was brought to the E.R. following a car accident,
有大范围的内出血  然后仓促进行手术
rushed into surgery with massive internal bleeding.
你和我是主刀医生  尽管尽了最大的努力
You joined me,and in spite of our most heroic efforts,
病人还是没能挺过来
the patient succumbed to her injuries.
看来除了病人  你把每件事都做得很完美
Looks like you fixed everything but the patient.
你在手术室没有认真工作
You had no business being in O.R.
你真以为如果碰上我应付不了的手术  我会走进手术室?
You really think I would have walked in there if I couldn't handle it?
你以前这么做过
You've done it before.
说得对  我有过  因为我有能力完美地把那些...
That's right,I have,because I am perfectly capable of making those ...
发生昨天那样的事  你居然还敢这么说?
How can you say that after what happened yesterday?
-问题不是...  -你的价值降低了
-The problem is not...  -You were impaired.
-我知道我的能力界限在哪  -我不会签这个字的
-I know my limits.  -I won't sign this.
你是小组中的一员  Jack
You were part of a team,Jack.
我不是唯一一个和这件事挂钩的
I'm not the only one on the hook for this.
你接替我做的手术
You called me off.
她死的时候档案里记录  你是主刀医生
You were the surgeon of record when she died.
听着  手术过程中发生意外是常有的事  Jack
Look,accidents happen in surgeries all the time,Jack.
那就是事实  你知道的
That's the truth,and you know it.
如果你抵触这份报告
But if you contradict this report,
如果你提到酒
if you mention alcohol,
那将会是造成事故的唯一事实
well,that's the only fact that's gonna matter.
他们会吊销我的执照的
They'll strip me of my license.
是的...
Yes...
他们会的
they will.
我知道我对你管教很严
I know I have been hard on you,
那是因为我恨铁不成钢
but that is how you make a soft metal into steel.
所以你才会成为
That is why
本市最有天赋的年轻外科医生
you are the most gifted young surgeon in this city.
我意思是  这是...
I mean,this...
这是一个可以带来很大好处的职业
this is a career that is all about the greater good.
在你和我关系上的某些方面...
I've had to sacrifice
我不得不做出牺牲
certain aspects of my relationship with you
那样成百上千的病人...
so that hundreds and thousands of patients will live
会因为你高超的技术而活着
because of your extraordinary skills.
我知道这要等...
I know it's a long...
很长的时间
long time coming.
但昨天发生的事
What happened yesterday,
我向你保证
I promise you,
再也不会发生了
will never happen again.
我已经付出了那么多...
After what I've given...
这不只....这已经不只关系到我的职业  Jack
this isn't...this is not just about my career,Jack,
这是我的生命
it's my life.
谢谢你  儿子
Thank you,son.
我不知道你们伊斯兰教是否有命运这种概念
I don't know if you Islams got a concept of karma,
但我有种感觉  这个岛屿偿还了你很多东西
but I get the sense this island just served you up a heaping platter of cosmic payback.
你想干什么?
What do you want?
"正义"医生不肯给我抗生素
Dr. Do-right doesn't trust me with his antibiotics
所以我只能每天自己来这儿取药了
so I gotta hump it up here every day to get my meds.
你知道  一个比我还没有雅量的人
You know,a less magnanimous man than I
也会觉得能够痛扁眼前这个苟且偷生的贱人
might just be thinking he could beat the ever-living snot out of you right now
而不必担心报复
without fear of reprisal.
你想打就打吧
You want a shot,take it.
但我要你知道  我离开是因为对自己的所作所为感到羞耻
Know that I left this camp out of shame for what I did to you.
我决不是故意要回来的
It was never my intention to return.
抱歉  我对请求宽容这种事已经免疫了
Sorry,fresh out of sweet forgiveness.
如果不是故意的  那你为什么要回来?
If it wasn't your intention to return,then why did you?
我被那个法国女子俘虏了
I was taken prisoner by the Frenchwoman.
那个发送了16年求救信号的法国女子?
The one that's been sending out a distress signal for 16 years?
她还活着?
She's alive?
她是一支科考队的
She was on a science expedition.
她说他们的船只失事了
She said they shipwrecked.
她一个人?
She alone?
她说岛上还有其他人
She said that there are others on this island.
不是  她认为她队里的人都病了
No,she believed they had all gotten sick.
她杀了整支科考队
She murdered her entire team.
那其他人他妈的又是谁?
And these others,who the hell are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
她从没看到过他们
She's never seen them.
她从没看到过他们  却知道他们在那儿?
Oh,she's never seen them,but she knows they're there?
如果你相信她的话
If you believe her.
或许不相信
Maybe not.
但在我回来的路上
But on my way back,
我听到丛林里有东西...
I heard something in the jungle...
围绕着我
surrounding me.
什么东西?
Something like what?
你还有什么要说的吗  Sawyer?
Have you got something to say to me,Sawyer?
还是继续问我  连我都不知道答案的问题?
Or are you going to continue asking me questions you know I don't have the answers to?
潮水涨到岸上了
Tide's coming up the beach.
机身几乎浸在水里了
The plane hull's almost in the water.
我继续用你的烧火方式求救
I kept your signal fire burning.
你孤立的棋子进不来了
Your blots can't get in.
是的  我知道那颗孤立的棋子进不来了
Yeah,I know my blots can't get in.
-轮到我掷骰子了  -喔哦!
-My roll.  -Yahoo!
我需要一个三  一个四
I need a four-three.
小子  你能不能快点?
Dude,would you please roll?
-好!  -不!
-Yes!  -No!
轮到你了
Your turn.
没事
It's okay.
我第一次玩的时候玩得也不好
I wasn't very good when I first started playing,either.
我不是第一次玩
I didn't just start playing.
我在联赛中获得了第17名
I took 17th in a tournament once.
-17名不怎么好啊  -不  17名很好
-17th is not very good.  -No,17th is very good.
拜托了  两个六  两个六
Come on,double sixes,double sixes.
-好!  -开什么玩笑
-Yes!  -Oh,you gotta be kidding me.
-我很幸运  -没人会那么幸运
-I'm lucky.  -No one is that lucky.
我爸爸说我是他认识的人中最幸运的家伙
My dad said I was the luckiest person he ever knew.
真的吗?
Really?
不是Michael  是Brian  我的另一个爸爸
Not Michael...Brian,my other dad.
是的
Yeah,um...
好!  好!
Yes! Yes!
来吧  再来一局  要么加倍付钱  要么一笔购销
Come on,one more game. Double or nothing.
我不能来了
I can't.
-会议?  -是的  一个会议
-A meeting?  -Yeah,a meeting.
-你欠我2000美元  -会给你的
-You owe me $20,000.  -You'll get it.
我们已经有15分钟没看到任何踪迹了
It's been about 15 minutes since we've seen any sign.
我们在跟踪什么?
What are we following?
-我的勇气  -很好
-My gut.  -Great.
那么Boone  在现实生活中你是干什么的?
So,Boone,what do you do in the real world?
我做生意的
I run a business.
-什么生意?  -一些婚礼的东西
-What kind of business?  -It's a wedding thing.
我妈妈有个大企业
My mother has this empire...
玛莎·斯图而特婚姻公司
the Martha Stewart of matrimony.
我经营其中一个子公司
I run one of the subsidiaries.
那么现在由谁管呢?
So,who's running it now?
这已经不重要了  不是吗?
I guess it doesn't matter,does it?
我想会有人临时接管的
I'm sure there are people who can handle it temporarily.
一分钟后将下雨
It's gonna start raining in one minute.
-一分钟?  -几秒种的偏差
-One minute?  -Give or take a few seconds.
你应该折回  Boone  回去
You should turn around,Boone,head back.
什么?
What?
已经有1/4英里我们没看到踪迹了  前面很危险
Trail's been cold for 1/4 mile,dangerous terrain ahead.
如果你现在回去就能在天黑前赶到营地
If you start now,you'll make it back to camp before dark.
-那你呢?  -我会照顾好自己
-What about you?  -I can take care of myself.
我欣赏你的勇气  但你应该...
I admire your courage,but you should...
我不会回去的
I'm not heading back.
好吧
All right.
在包装箱公司他们教你如何预测天气?
They teach you how to predict the weather at a box company?
我想我们走对了
I guess we were right.
现在往哪儿走?
Where to now?
Jack!
Jack  你去哪儿?
Jack, where are you going?
你听到她了吗?
Didn't you hear her?
听到谁?
Hear who?
Jack!
如果你再跟着我
If you do not stop following me,
我会杀了他们其中一个
I will kill one of them.
明白吗?
Do you understand?
不会警告你第二遍
No more warnings.
Shephard医生
Dr. Shephard.
Andrea
Andrea...
和我父亲说话的那人是谁?
That man that my father's talking to...who is that?
是那病人的丈夫
That's her husband.
他威胁说要起诉
He's threatening to sue.
Jack
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
我昏了多久了?
How long was I out?
我不知道  几分钟吧  你滑倒了  岩石什么的都掉下来了
I don't know,a few minutes. You slipped. With all the rocks and everything.
-Ethan  -什么?
-Ethan.  -What?
-Ethan在这儿  -你撞到头了  Jack
-Ethan was here.  -You banged your head,Jack.
不  不  他不在这儿
No,no. He was here.
你得停手了
You have to stop.
雨水把痕迹都冲掉了
The rain has washed away the trail.
即使他在这儿  你也得...Jack!
Even if he was here,you've got...Jack!
我不会再让他这么做的
I'm not letting him do this.
-不让他?  -不再让了
-Not letting him?  -Not again.
我们发现她的血压急速下降
We realized that her blood pressure was continuing to drop precipitously.
此刻  病人的心脏停止跳动
At which point,the patient went into cardiac arrest.
当然  我们尽了最大的努力抢救
Of course,every effort was made to resuscitate her,
但是严重的伤势...
but the severity of her injuries...
以及大量的内出血使得我们无力挽救她的生命
the amount of internal bleeding made that impossible.
按照我的职业观点  女士们先生们  我要说的是...
Now,in my professional opinion,ladies and gentlemen,and that's all I have...
当我赶到的时候  形势已经无法逆转了
by the time I was called in,the damage was irreversible.
好的  谢谢  Christian
Okay. Thanks,Christian.
-我们对这种形式主义感到抱歉  -好的
-Sorry about this formality.  -Of course.
最后一个细节
Just one final detail.
你动手术的时候知道病人已经怀孕了吗?
You were aware of the patient's pregnancy when you went into the procedure?
病人的丈夫为预产的事来过急诊室
The patient's husband had informed the attending in the E.R.
不过是在怀孕很早期的时候
It was,however,extremely early in the pregnancy
所以我们把重点主要放在母亲身上
so our primary focus had to be on the mother.
好的  那么  我想我们问完了
Okay,then,I think we're done here.
最终结果将做成档案
Our final report will be filed.
好的
Okay.
我需要...
I need to...
修正一下我的陈述词
revise my statement.
我是了解情况以后才进的手术室
I didn't come into the O.R. until well into the procedure.
Jack
我被一个护士提醒  我父亲在受影响的情况下...
I was warned by one of the nurses that my father was operating...
给病人动手术
under the influence.
等我赶到那的时候  很明显我父亲已经...
By the time I got there,it was clear that my father was
无法控制局面了  同时他还...
not only incapacitated,but that he had also...
割断了病人的肝动脉
severed the patient's hepatic artery,
按照我的职业观点
which,in my professional opinion,
这造成了病人的最终死亡
caused the crisis which led to her death.
不!
No!
你去把绳子割断
You gotta cut him down.
坚持住  Charlie  坚持住
Hold on,Charlie. Hold on there.
我够不到!  拉他过来!
I can't reach! Pull him over!
他停止呼吸了
He's not breathing.
加油  呼吸
Come on,breathe.
呼吸  Charlie  加油  呼吸!
Breathe,Charlie,come on. Breathe!
加油
Come on.
加油!
Come on!
Jack
加油  Charlie!  加油!
Come on,Charlie! Come on!
加油  加油
Come on. Come on.
加油  Charlie  加油!
Come on,Charlie. Come on!
加油!
Come on!
加油  Charlie  加油!
Come on,Charlie. Come on!
加油!
Come on!
Jack
Jack  Jack
Jack  他...Jack  不要打了  他不会回来了...
Jack,he's...Jack,stop. He's not coming...
没关系的  没关系的
It's okay. It's okay.
不
No.
Jack!
加油
Come on.
好的
Yeah.
好  尽量呼吸  呼吸
Yeah, just breathe. Breathe.
就这样
That's it.
作深呼吸  深呼吸
Just breathe deep. Breathe deep.
做得好
There you are.
你没事了
You're okay.
他们把Charlie带回来了  但他回来后还没说过话
They brought Charlie back,but he hasn't said anything since he came back.
他们找到Claire了?
They find Claire?
疼吗?
Does that hurt?
呼吸怎样了?
How's your breathing?
Charlie...
你得和我说话
you gotta talk to me.
太阳一出来  我们就要回去找Claire了
We're gonna go back out and look for Claire the moment the sun comes up.
我真的很需要你的帮助
And I could really use your help.
我是说  任何你可以告诉我们的有关...
I mean,anything that you can tell me about...
你记得的事情  你去过哪了
what you remember,where you were going.
你有没看到或听到...
Did you see or hear...
我什么都没看到...
I didn't see anything...
什么都没听到
hear anything.
我什么都不记得了...
I don't remember...
什么都记不起来了
anything.
Claire
什么?
What?
才是他们想要的
That's all they wanted.
"他们"
"They."
他们想要的是Claire
All they wanted was Claire.
他们还没回来
They aren't back yet.
我确信他们在那儿扎营过夜了
I'm sure they just made camp for the night.
要说你哥哥跟岛上谁在一起最安全
If there's anyone on this island that your brother's safe with,
只有Locke了
it's Locke.
我们迷路了吗?
Are we lost?
不  Boone  我们没迷路
No,Boone,we're not lost.
对不起  只是...
Sorry,it's just...
我不明白你怎么还能继续跟踪?
I don't see how you can still be following his trail.
我想我们该回去了  老兄
I think we should go back,man.
你没感觉到吗?
Don't you feel it?
-感觉什么?  -它
-Feel what?  -It.
好吧  John
All right,John,
我要沿着红条标记折回了
I'm gonna follow the strips back.
自己看着办吧
Suit yourself.
Boone
你比我更需要这个
You need this more than I do.
那是什么?
What is that?
铁的
Steel.
那是飞机的一部分...
Could that be part of the plane...
失事飞机的一部分吗?
part of the wreckage?
这是什么?
What is that?
这就是我们要找的了
That's what we're gonna find out.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====